l want to make a good impression.
No offense, but with you here...
...l look like I'm 6'2".
The nuns always chaperoned
the dances at my high school.
(Bernadette:)They used to make us leave room
between us for the Holy Spirit.
Hmm.
(Howard:)Hindus do the same thing.
Except they leave room for a cow. Ha, ha.
(Raj:)Listen, I love your charming
racist humor.
But any chance you could not mock
my religion while she's here?
(Howard:)- You made fun of me for eating lox.
- Your people don't worship lox.
(Howard:)Clearly you've never been to brunch
with my cousins.
(Bernadette:)So arranged marriages,
the parents just decide...
...and then you get married?
Oh, no, no. I get a say in it. I'm sure
whoever shows up will be better company...
...than the threesome l've been having
with Aunt Jemima and Mrs. Butterworth.
(Girl:)Excuse me, are you Rajesh?
(Raj:)Oh, yes. You must be Lakshmi.
(Raj:)- Uh, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you too.
Oh, uh, these are my friends.
Uh, this is Bernadette.
- Hello.
- Uh, and this is Howard.